Rick Whitesell Record Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 3. 7" Discs, 3; 12 linear feet Boxes: 1 - 23 Folders: 3.7.1 - 3.7.1883
  - George Greeley, Record Label:Reprise (Folder 997, Box 13)
    - Caeser and Cleopatra, 2
  - John Greer&His Rhythm Rockers, Record Label:RCA Victor (Folder 998, Box 13)
    - I'm The Fat Man, 1
    - Since You Went Away From Me, 2
  - Shirley Gunter&The Flairs, Record Label:Modern Hollywood (Folder 999, Box 13)
    - Headin' Home, 1
    - I Want You, 2
  - Sammy Hagan&The Viscounts, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 1000, Box 13)
    - Snuggle Bunny, 1
    - Tail Light, 2
  - Bill Haley And His Comets, Record Label:Warner Bros. (Folder 1001, Box 13)
    - Tamiami, 1
    - Candy Kisses, 2
  - Jim Hall And His Orchestra, Record Label:May (Folder 1002, Box 13)
    - Lawrence Of Arabia, 1
    - 2
  - Larry Hall, Record Label:Strand (Folder 1003, Box 13)
    - Sandy, 1
    - Lovin' Tree, 2
  - George Hamilton IV, Record Label:RCA Victor (Folder 1004, Box 13)
    - If You Don't Somebody Else Will, 1
    - There's More Pretty Girls Than One, 2
  - George Hamilton IV, Record Label:ABC Paramount (Folder 1005, Box 13)
    - A Rose And A Baby Ruth, 1
    - If You Don't Know, 2
  - Roy Hamilton, Record Label:Epic (Folder 1006, Box 13)
    - Beware, 1
    - Ebb Tide, 2
  - Roy Hamilton, Record Label:Epic (Folder 1007, Box 13)
    - A Simple Prayer, 1
    - A Mother's Love, 2
  - Roy Hamilton, Record Label:Epic (Folder 1008, Box 13)
    - Everything, 1
    - Wait For Me, 2
  - Roy Hamilton, Record Label:Epic (Folder 1009, Box 13)
    - Don't Let Go, 1
    - The Right To Love, 2
  - Roy Hamilton, Record Label:Epic (Folder 1010, Box 13)
    - I Believe, 1
    - If You Are But A Dream, 2
  - Roy Hamilton, Record Label:Epic (Folder 1011, Box 13)
    - Since I Fell For You, 1
    - Somebody Somewhere, 2
  - Roy Hamilton, Record Label:Epic (Folder 1012, Box 13)
    - Pledging My Love, 1
    - My One And Only Love, 2
  - Roy Hamilton, Record Label:Epic 2 copies (Folder 1013, Box 13)
    - You're Gonna Need Magic, 1
    - To The One I Love, 2
  - Roy Hamilton, Record Label:Epic (Folder 1014, Box 13)
    - If I Loved You, 1
    - So Let There Be Love, 2
  - Roy Hamilton, Record Label:Epic (Folder 1015, Box 13)
    - Climb Ev'ry Mountain, 1
    - I'll Come Running Back To You, 2
  - Roy Hamilton, Record Label:Epic (Folder 1016, Box 13)
    - I'm Gonna Sit Right Down And Cry, 1
    - You'll Never Walk Alone, 2
  - Roy Hamilton, Record Label:Epic (Folder 1017, Box 13)
    - (All Of A Sudden) My Heart Sings, 1
    - I'm Gonna Lock You In My Heart (And Lose the Key), 2
  - Roy Hamilton, Record Label:Epic (Folder 1018, Box 13)
    - Take It Easy, Joe, 1
    - Time Marches On, 2
  - The Happenings, Record Label:B.T. Puppy (Folder 1019, Box 13)
    - I Believe In Nothing, 1
    - My Mammy, 2
  - Slim Harpo, Record Label:Excello (Folder 1020, Box 13)
    - Baby Scratch My Back, 1
    - I'm Gonna Miss You, 2
  - Slim Harpo, Record Label:Excello (Folder 1021, Box 13)
    - Don't Start Cryin' Now, 1
    - Rainin' In My Heart, 2
  - The Harptones, Record Label:Andrea (Folder 1022, Box 13)
    - What Is Your Decision, 1
    - Gimmie Some, 2
  - The Harptones, Record Label:Bruce (Folder 1023, Box 13)
    - My Memories Of You, 1
    - It Was Just For Laughs, 2
  - The Harptones, Record Label:Bruce (Folder 1024, Box 13)
    - I'll Never Tell, 1
    - Sunday Kind Of Love, 2
  - The Harptones, Record Label:Paradise (Folder 1025, Box 13)
    - You Know You're Doing Me Wrong, 1
    - Life Is But A Dream, 2
  - The Harptones, Record Label:Rama (Folder 1026, Box 13)
    - On Sunday Afternoon, 1
    - The Masquerade Is Over, 2
  - The Harptones, Record Label:Rama (Folder 1027, Box 13)
    - Three Wishes, 1
    - That's The Way It Goes, 2
  - The Harptones, Record Label:Raven (Folder 1028, Box 13)
    - Mambo Boogie, 1
    - Sunday Kind Of Love, 2
  - The Harptones, Record Label:Warwick (Folder 1029, Box 13)
    - What Kind Of Fool, 1
    - No Greater Miracle, 2
  - Richard Harris, Record Label:Dunhill (Folder 1030, Box 13)
    - Didn't We, 1
    - Mac Arthur Park, 2
  - Thurston Harris, Record Label:Aladdin (Folder 1031, Box 13)
    - Little Bitty Pretty One, 1
    - I Hope You Won't Hold It Against Me, 2
  - Wilbert Harrison, Record Label:Fury 2 copies (Folder 1032, Box 13)
    - Kansas City, 1
    - Listen, My Darling, 2
  - Harvey, Record Label:Chess (Folder 1033, Box 13)
    - I Want Somebody, 1
    - Da Da Goo Goo, 2
  - Harvey And The Moonglows, Record Label:Chess (Folder 1034, Box 13)
    - Mean Old Blues, 1
    - Ten Commandments Of Love, 2
  - Shirly Haven&The Four Jacks, Record Label:Federal (Folder 1035, Box 13)
    - Troubles Of My Own, 1
    - Stop Fooling Around, 2
  - Haven Knights, Record Label:Angle Tone (Folder 1036, Box 13)
    - In My Lonely Room, 1
    - I'm Just A Dreamer, 2
  - Haven Knights, Record Label:Sold (Folder 1037, Box 13)
    - Why Go On Pretending, 1
    - Just To Be In Love, 2
  - Sam Hawkins, Record Label:Gone (Folder 1038, Box 13)
    - King Of Fools, 1
    - The Whatchamacallit, 2
  - Lee Hazlewood, Record Label:M G M (Folder 1039, Box 13)
    - M G M, 1
    - Sand, 2
  - Roy Head, Record Label:Scepter (Folder 1040, Box 13)
    - Get Back (Vocal), 1
    - Get Back (Instrumental), 2
  - The Heartbeats, Record Label:Gee (Folder 1041, Box 13)
    - After New Year's Eve, 1
    - 500 Miles To Go, 2
  - The Heartbeats, Record Label:Gee (Folder 1042, Box 13)
    - Hurry Home, Baby, 1
    - Darling, How Long, 2
  - The Heartbeats, Record Label:Gee (Folder 1043, Box 13)
    - Hands Off My Baby, 1
    - When I Found You, 2
  - The Heartbeats, Record Label:Guyden (Folder 1044, Box 13)
    - One Million Years, 1
    - Darling, I Want To Get Married, 2
  - The Heartbeats, Record Label:Hull (Folder 1045, Box 13)
    - Your Way, 1
    - People Are Talking, 2
  - The Heartbeats, Record Label:Hull (Folder 1046, Box 13)
    - A Thousand Miles Away, 1
    - Oh Baby Don't, 2
  - The Heartbeats, Record Label:Rama (Folder 1047, Box 13)
    - A Thousand Miles Away, 1
    - Oh Baby Don't, 2
  - The Heartbeats, Record Label:Roulette (Folder 1048, Box 13)
    - Crazy For You, 1
    - Down On My Knees, 2
  - The Hearts, Record Label:Baton (Folder 1049, Box 13)
    - Oo-Wee, 1
    - Lonely Nights, 2
  - Bobby Hebb, Record Label:Philips (1050, Box 14)
    - Bread, 1
    - Sunny, 2
  - Bobby Helms, Record Label:Decca (Folder 1051, Box 14)
    - Living In The Shadow Of The Past, 1
    - Jacqueline, 2
  - Bobby Helms, Record Label:Decca (Folder 1052, Box 14)
    - Standing At The End Of My World, 1
    - My Special Angel, 2
  - Clarence Henry "Frog Man", Record Label:Argo (Folder 1053, Box 14)
    - Troubles, Troubles, 1
    - Ain't Got No Home, 2
  - Clarence Henry "Frog Man", Record Label:Parrot (Folder 1054, Box 14)
    - Little Green Frog, 1
    - Have You Ever Been Lonely, 2
  - Clarence Henry "Frog Man", Record Label:Argo (Folder 1055, Box 14)
    - Why Can't You, 1
    - Lonely Street, 2
  - Clarence Henry "Frog Man", Record Label:Argo (Folder 1056, Box 14)
    - Lost Without You, 1
    - Dream Myself A Sweetheart, 2
  - Clarence Henry "Frog Man", Record Label:Argo (Folder 1057, Box 14)
    - On Bended Knees, 1
    - Standing In The Need Of Love, 2
  - Clarence Henry, Record Label:Argo (Folder 1058, Box 14)
    - You Always Hurt The One You Love, 1
    - Little Suzy, 2
  - Herman's Hermits, Record Label:M G M (Folder 1059, Box 14)
    - Just A Little Bit Better, 1
    - Sea Cruise, 2
  - Herman's Hermits, Record Label:M G M (Folder 1060, Box 14)
    - Mrs. Brown You've Got A Lovely Daughter, 1
    - I Gotta Dream On, 2
  - Herman's Hermits, Record Label:M G M (Folder 1061, Box 14)
    - Walkin' With My Angel, 1
    - Silhouettes, 2
  - Ersel Hickey, Record Label:Epic (Folder 1062, Box 14)
    - Bluebirds Over The Mountain, 1
    - Hangin' Around, 2
  - Charlie Hicks, Record Label:Callico (Folder 1063, Box 14)
    - Impressed, 1
    - Tonight, 2
  - The Hide-A-Ways, Record Label:Lost Nite (Folder 1064, Box 14)
    - I'm Coming Home, 1
    - Can't Help Loving That Girl Of Mine, 2
  - The Hi-Fives, Record Label:Decca (Folder 1065, Box 14)
    - My Friend, 1
    - How Can I Win, 2
  - The Highwaymen, Record Label:United Artists (Folder 1066, Box 14)
    - The Bird Man, 1
    - Cindy Oh Cindy, 2
  - The Highway Q.C.'s, Record Label:Vee-Jay (Folder 1067, Box 14)
    - How I Love Jesus, 1
    - Teach Me, 2
  - The Hilltoppers, Record Label:Dot (Folder 1068, Box 14)
    - No Regrets, 1
    - Until You're Mine, 2
  - The Hilltoppers, Record Label:Dot (Folder 1069, Box 14)
    - D-A-R-L-I-N', 1
    - Frivolette, 2
  - The Hi-Lites, Record Label:Record Fair (Folder 1070, Box 14)
    - I'm Falling In Love, 1
    - Walking My Baby Back Home, 2
  - The Hi-Lites, Record Label:Record Fair (Folder 1071, Box 14)
    - (I Love You) For Sentimental Reasons, 1
    - For Your Precious Love, 2
  - The Hi-Lo's, Record Label:Reprise (Folder 1072, Box 14)
    - A Taste Of Honey, 1
    - My Baby Just Cares For Me, 2
  - The Hi-Lo's with Ray Ellis and His Orchestra, Record Label:Columbia (Folder 1073, Box 14)
    - A Very Special Love, 1
    - My Sugar Is So Refined, 2
  - The Hitmakers, Record Label:Original Sound (Folder 1074, Box 14)
    - Cool School, 1
    - Chapel Of Love, 2
  - The Holidays, Record Label:Melba (Folder 1075, Box 14)
    - Desperately, 1
    - The Robin, 2
  - The Hollies, Record Label:Imperial (Folder 1076, Box 14)
    - Don't Run and Hide, 1
    - Bus Stop, 2
  - Buddy Holly, Record Label:Coral (Folder 1077, Box 14)
    - Raining in My Heart, 1
    - It Doesn’t Matter Anymore, 2
  - Hollywood Flames, Record Label:Ebb (Folder 1078, Box 14)
    - Crazy, 1
    - Buzz-Buzz-Buzz, 2
  - Hollywood Flames, Record Label:Ebb (Folder 1079, Box 14)
    - A Little Bird, 1
    - Give Me Back My Heart, 2
  - Hollywood Flames, Record Label:Ebb (Folder 1080, Box 14)
    - In The Dark, 1
    - Much Too Much, 2
  - Hollywood Flames, Record Label:Goldie (Folder 1081, Box 14)
    - Believe In Me, 1
    - Elizabeth, 2
  - The Hollywood Saxons, Record Label:Relic (Folder 1082, Box 14)
    - Is It True?, 1
    - Rock And Roll Show, 2
  - Homer And Jethro, Record Label:RCA Victor (Folder 1083, Box 14)
    - That's Good, That's Bad, 1
    - El Paso- Numero Dos, 2
  - The Hondas, Record Label:Eden (Folder 1084, Box 14)
    - Send It, 1
    - Twelve Feet High, 2
  - The Hondells, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1085, Box 14)
    - Sea Cruise, 1
    - You Meet The Nicest People On A Honda, 2
  - The Honey Bees, Record Label:Imperial (Folder 1086, Box 14)
    - Endless, 1
    - Let's See What's Happening, 2
  - John Lee Hooker, Record Label:Battle (Folder 1087, Box 14)
    - No More Doggin', 1
    - I Need Some Money, 2
  - John Lee Hooker, Record Label:Vee-Jay (Folder 1088, Box 14)
    - You've Taken My Woman, 1
    - I Love You Honey, 2
  - Lightnin' Hopkins, Record Label:Prestige Bluesville (Folder 1089, Box 14)
    - Hard To Love A Woman, 1
    - Back To New Orleans, 2
  - The Hot Shots, Record Label:Savoy (Folder 1090, Box 14)
    - Blue Dreams, 1
    - Blue Nights, 2
  - Helen Humes, Record Label:Modern Hollywood (Folder 1091, Box 14)
    - I Ain't In The Mood, 1
    - Living My Life My Way, 2
  - Herbert Hunter, Record Label:Spar (Folder 1092, Box 14)
    - I Was Born To Love You, 1
    - Push Away From The Table, 2
  - Ivory Joe Hunter, Record Label:Atlantic (Folder 1093, Box 14)
    - You Can't Stop This Rocking And Rolling, 1
    - You Can't Stop This Rocking And Rolling, 2
  - Ivory Joe Hunter, Record Label:Atlantic EP (Folder 1094, Box 14)
    - It May Sound Silly, 1
    - A Tear Fell, 2
    - Since I Met You Baby, 3
    - I Got To Learn To Do The Mambo, 4
  - The Hurricanes, Record Label:King (Folder 1095, Box 14)
    - Yours, 1
    - Maybe It's All For The Best, 2
  - The Ideals, Record Label:Checker (Folder 1096, Box 14)
    - Knee Socks, 1
    - Mary's Lamb, 2
  - The Imaginations, Record Label:Music Maker (Folder 1097, Box 14)
    - Hey You, 1
    - Guardian Angel, 2
  - The Impalas, Record Label:Cub (Folder 1098, Box 14)
    - Oh, What A Fool, 1
    - Sandy Went Away, 2
  - The Impalas, Record Label:Cub (Folder 1099, Box 14)
    - Fool, Fool, Fool, 1
    - Sorry (I Ran All The Way Home), 2
  - The Imperials, Record Label:End (Folder 1100, Box 14)
    - Two People In The World, 1
    - Tears On My Pillow, 2
  - The Imperials, Record Label:Savoy Test Pressing (Folder 1101, Box 14)
    - My Darling, 1
    - You Should Have Told Me, 2
  - The Impressions, Record Label:Abner (Folder 1102, Box 14)
    - Love Me, 1
    - Come Back My Love, 2
  - The Impressions, Record Label:Abner (Folder 1103, Box 14)
    - I Made A Mistake, 1
    - I'm So Proud, 2
  - The Ink Spots, Record Label:Decca (Folder 1104, Box 14)
    - Always, 1
    - White Christmas, 2
  - The Ink Spots, Record Label:Decca (Folder 1105, Box 14)
    - Maybe, 1
    - We Three, 2
  - The Ink Spots, Record Label:Decca (Folder 1106, Box 14)
    - Whispering Grass, 1
    - If I Didn't Care, 2
  - The Ink Spots, Record Label:Decca (Folder 1107, Box 14)
    - I'll Get By, 1
    - Just For A Thrill, 2
  - The Ink Spots, Record Label:Decca (Folder 1108, Box 14)
    - I'll Never Smile Again, 1
    - Until The Real Thing Comes Along, 2
  - The Ink Spots, Record Label:Decca (Folder 1109, Box 14)
    - To Each His Own, 1
    - I Never Had A Dream Come True, 2
  - The Ink Spots, Record Label:Decca (Folder 1110, Box 14)
    - It's A Sin To Tell A Lie, 1
    - That's When Your Heartaches Begin, 2
  - The Ink Spots, Record Label:Decca (Folder 1111, Box 14)
    - The Gypsy, 1
    - Everyone Is Saying Hello Again (Why Must We Say Goodbye?), 2
  - The Ink Spots, Record Label:Decca (Folder 1112, Box 14)
    - I'm Gettin' Sentimental Over You, 1
    - I'd Climb The Highest Mountain (If I Knew I'd Find You), 2
  - The Ink Spots, Record Label:Decca EP (Folder 1113, Box 14)
    - Address Unknown, 1
    - Don't Get Around Much Anymore, 2
    - Street Of Dreams, 3
    - Please Take A Letter Miss Brown, 4
  - The Ink Spots, Record Label:King (Folder 1114, Box 14)
    - If You Should Say Goodbye, 1
    - Ebb Tide, 2
  - The Inspirations, Record Label:Apollo (Folder 1115, Box 14)
    - Maggie, 1
    - Raindrops (The Crying Song), 2
  - The Inspirations, Record Label:Jamie (Folder 1116, Box 14)
    - Good By, 1
    - Dry Your Eyes, 2
  - The Interludes, Record Label:King (Folder 1117, Box 14)
    - Darling, I'll Be True, 1
    - Wilted Rose Bud, 2
  - The Internes, Record Label:Vee-Jay (Folder 1118, Box 14)
    - The Road Home, 1
    - When You Pray, 2
  - The Ivories, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1119, Box 14)
    - Me And You, 1
    - I'm In Love, 2
  - Jackie&The Starlites, Record Label:Fury (Folder 1120, Box 14)
    - I Found Out Too Late, 1
    - I'm Coming Home, 2
  - The Jacks, Record Label:Kent (Folder 1121, Box 14)
    - This Empty Heart, 1
    - Why Don't You Write Me, 2
  - The Jacks, Record Label:RPM (Folder 1122, Box 14)
    - This Empty Heart, 1
    - My Clumsy Heart, 2
  - The Jacks, Record Label:RPM (Folder 1123, Box 14)
    - How Soon, 1
    - So Wrong, 2
  - Mahalia Jackson, Record Label:Columbia (Folder 1124, Box 14)
    - One God, 1
    - You'll Never Walk Alone, 2
  - Stoney Jackson&The V-Eights, Record Label:Vibro (Folder 1125, Box 14)
    - Hot Water, 1
    - Let's Take A Chance, 2
  - The Jaguars, Record Label:Aardell (Folder 1126, Box 14)
    - I Wanted You, 1
    - Rock It, Davy, Rock It, 2
  - Elmo James, Record Label:Sphere Sound (Folder 1127, Box 14)
    - Dust My Broom, 1
    - Rollin' And Tumblin', 2
  - Elmore James, Record Label:Enjoy (Folder 1128, Box 14)
    - It Hurts Me Too, 1
    - Pickin' The Blues, 2
  - Jan And Dean, Record Label:Liberty (Folder 1129, Box 14)
    - Poor Little Puppet, 1
    - A Sunday Kind Of Love, 2
  - Jan&The Radiants, Record Label:Queen (Folder 1130, Box 14)
    - If You Love Me, 1
    - Is It True (I Still Believe In You), 2
  - The Jarmels, Record Label:Laurie (Folder 1131, Box 14)
    - The Way You Look Tonight, 1
    - A Little Bit Of Soap, 2
  - The Jayhawks, Record Label:Flash (Folder 1132, Box 14)
    - My Only Darling, 1
    - Stranded In The Jungle, 2
  - The Jaytones, Record Label:Cub (Folder 1133, Box 14)
    - My Only Love, 1
    - Absolutely Right, 2
  - The Jesters, Record Label:Cyclone (Folder 1134, Box 14)
    - I Laughed, 1
    - Now That You're Gone, 2
  - The Jesters, Record Label:Winley (Folder 1135, Box 14)
    - The Wind, 1
    - Sally Green, 2
  - The Jesters, Record Label:Winley (Folder 1136, Box 14)
    - So Strange, 1
    - Love No One But You, 2
  - The Jesters, Record Label:Winley (Folder 1137, Box 14)
    - Uncle Henry's Basement, 1
    - Come Let Me Show You, 2
  - Jeanie&Her Boy Friends, Record Label:Warwick (1138, Box 15)
    - Baby, 1
    - It's Me Knockin', 2
  - Gus Jinkins, Record Label:Flash (Folder 1139, Box 15)
    - Tricky, 1
    - You Told Me, 2
  - The Jive Bombers, Record Label:Savoy (Folder 1140, Box 15)
    - Bad Boy, 1
    - When Your Hair Has Turned To Silver, 2
  - The Jive Five, Record Label:Beltone (Folder 1141, Box 15)
    - Hully Gully Callin' Time, 1
    - No Not Again, 2
  - The Jive Five, Record Label:Beltone (Folder 1142, Box 15)
    - Beggin' You Please, 1
    - What Time Is It?, 2
  - The Jive Five, Record Label:Beltone (Folder 1143, Box 15)
    - When I Was Single, 1
    - My True Story, 2
  - The Jive Five, Record Label:Beltone (Folder 1144, Box 15)
    - These Golden Rings, 1
    - Do You Hear Wedding Bells, 2
  - The Jive Five, Record Label:Beltone (Folder 1145, Box 15)
    - Never, Never, 1
    - People From Another World, 2
  - The Jive Five, Record Label:United Artists (Folder 1146, Box 15)
    - Kiss, Kiss, Kiss, 1
    - I'm A Happy Man, 2
  - Joan And Joy, Record Label:Hull (Folder 1147, Box 15)
    - You're My Prescription, 1
    - My Lover Has Left Me, 2
  - Joey&The Lexingtons, Record Label:Dunes (Folder 1148, Box 15)
    - Bobbie, 1
    - Tears From My Eyes, 2
  - Johnnie&Joe, Record Label:Chess (Folder 1149, Box 15)
    - Feel Alright, 1
    - I'll Be Spinning, 2
  - Johnnie&Joe, Record Label:Chess (Folder 1150, Box 15)
    - Over The Mountain, Across The Sea, 1
    - My Baby's Gone, On, On, 2
  - Johnnie&Joe, Record Label:J&S (Folder 1151, Box 15)
    - Warm Soft And Lovely, 1
    - False Love Has Got To Go, 2
  - Johnnie&Joe, Record Label:J&S (Folder 1152, Box 15)
    - It Was There, 1
    - There Goes My Heart, 2
  - Betty Johnson, Record Label:Bally (Folder 1153, Box 15)
    - If It's Wrong To Love You, 1
    - I Dreamed, 2
  - Buddy Johnson, Record Label:RCA Victor (Folder 1154, Box 15)
    - Windbag, 1
    - I Heard That Song Before, 2
  - Buddy Johnson, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1155, Box 15)
    - Kool Kitty, 1
    - Why Don't Cha Stop It, 2
  - Buddy Johnson, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1156, Box 15)
    - Doot Doot Dow, 1
    - I Don't Want Nobody (To Have My Love But You), 2
  - Buddy Johnson, Record Label:Wing (Folder 1157, Box 15)
    - I Still Love You, 1
    - Goodbye Baby, 2
  - Eddie Johnson, Record Label:Chess (Folder 1158, Box 15)
    - Walk Softly, 1
    - Cold, Cold Heart, 2
  - Lonnie Johnson, Record Label:Groove (Folder 1159, Box 15)
    - Fly Right Baby, 1
    - He's A Jelly-Roll Baker, 2
  - Marv Johnson, Record Label:United Artists (Folder 1160, Box 15)
    - Whisper, 1
    - Come To Me, 2
  - Harmon "Hump" Jones, Record Label:Vision (Folder 1161, Box 15)
    - Lookin' For My Baby, 1
    - Pack Your Clothes, 2
  - Jimmy Jones, Record Label:Cub (Folder 1162, Box 15)
    - Handy Man, 1
    - The Search Is Over, 2
  - Jimmy Jones, Record Label:Cub (Folder 1163, Box 15)
    - Good Timin', 1
    - My Precious Angel, 2
  - Jimmie Jones And The Savoys, Record Label:Savoy (Folder 1164, Box 15)
    - Please Say You're Mine, 1
    - With All My Heart, 2
  - Jordan&The Fascinations, Record Label:Dapt (Folder 1165, Box 15)
    - My Imagination, 1
    - I'll Be Forever Loving You, 2
  - Louis Jordan, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1166, Box 15)
    - Big Bess, 1
    - Cat Scratchin', 2
  - Louis Jordan, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1167, Box 15)
    - Ain't Nobody Here But Us Chickens, 1
    - Choo Choo Ch Boogie, 2
  - Louis Jordan&His Tympany Five, Record Label:Aladdin (Folder 1168, Box 15)
    - Louie's Blues, 1
    - If I Had Any Sense I'd Go Back Home, 2
  - Louis Jordan&His Tympany Five, Record Label:"X" (Folder 1169, Box 15)
    - Bananas, 1
    - Baby Let's Do It Up, 2
  - Don Julian, Record Label:Dooto (Folder 1170, Box 15)
    - Heaven And Paradise, 1
    - Embarrassing Moments, 2
  - Don Julian, Record Label:Dootone (Folder 1171, Box 15)
    - Big Mama Wants To Rock, 1
    - Blue Moon, 2
  - The Kadaks, Record Label:J&S (Folder 1172, Box 15)
    - Don't Want No Teasing, 1
    - Look Up To The Sky, 2
  - Ernie K-Doe, Record Label:Minit (Folder 1173, Box 15)
    - Mother-In-Law, 1
    - Wanted $10,000.00 Reward, 2
  - The Keystones, Record Label:Epic (Folder 1174, Box 15)
    - The Magic Kiss, 1
    - After I Propose, 2
  - B.B. King, Record Label:Kent (Folder 1175, Box 15)
    - Just Like A Woman, 1
    - Eyesight To The Blind, 2
  - B.B. King, Record Label:RPM (Folder 1176, Box 15)
    - Quit My Baby, 1
    - Be Careful With A Fool, 2
  - B.B. King, Record Label:RPM (Folder 1177, Box 15)
    - Neighborhood Affair, 1
    - Please Hurry Home, 2
  - B.B. King, Record Label:RPM (Folder 1178, Box 15)
    - Bim Bam, 1
    - On My Word Of Honor, 2
  - B.B. King, Record Label:RPM (Folder 1179, Box 15)
    - I Want To Get Married, 1
    - Troubles, Troubles, Troubles, 2
  - B.B. King, Record Label:RPM (Folder 1180, Box 15)
    - Love You Baby, 1
    - The Woman I Love, 2
  - Ben E. King, Record Label:Atco (Folder 1181, Box 15)
    - Spanish Harlem, 1
    - First Taste Of Love, 2
  - Freddy King, Record Label:Federal (Folder 1182, Box 15)
    - You've Got To Love Her With A Feeling, 1
    - Have You Ever Loved A Woman?, 2
  - Mabel King, Record Label:Rama (Folder 1183, Box 15)
    - Second Hand Love, 1
    - Symbol Of Love, 2
  - The King Bees, Record Label:KRC (Folder 1184, Box 15)
    - Lovely Love, 1
    - Can't You Understand, 2
  - The King Pins, Record Label:Federal (Folder 1185, Box 15)
    - Two Hearts, 1
    - I Won't Have It, 2
  - The Kings And Queens, Record Label:Everlast (Folder 1186, Box 15)
    - I'm So Lonely, 1
    - Voices of Love, 2
  - The Bob Knight Four, Record Label:Laurel (Folder 1187, Box 15)
    - Good Goodby, 1
    - How Old Must I Be, 2
  - Marie Knight, Record Label:Wing (Folder 1188, Box 15)
    - Tell Me Why, 1
    - As Long As I Love, 2
  - Sonny Knight, Record Label:Dot (Folder 1189, Box 15)
    - Confidential, 1
    - Jail Bird, 2
  - The Knockouts, Record Label:Shad (Folder 1190, Box 15)
    - Darling Lorraine, 1
    - Riot In Room 3C, 2
  - Kurt Knundsen, Record Label:Golden Record (Folder 1191, Box 15)
    - Rumpelstiltskin, 1
    - The Nightingale (part 1), 2
    - The Nightingale (part 2), 3
    - The Pied Piper Of Hamelin, 4
  - The Kodoks, Record Label:Fury (Folder 1192, Box 15)
    - Make Believe World, 1
    - Oh Gee, Oh Gosh, 2
  - The Kodoks, Record Label:Fury (Folder 1193, Box 15)
    - Guardian Angel, 1
    - Run Around Baby, 2
  - The Ladders, Record Label:Holiday (Folder 1194, Box 15)
    - I Want to Know, 1
    - Counting The Stars, 2
  - The Laddins, Record Label:Central (Folder 1195, Box 15)
    - Did It, 1
    - Now You're Gone, 2
  - The Laddins, Record Label:Grey Cliff (Folder 1196, Box 15)
    - Yes, Oh Baby, Yes, 1
    - Light A Candle, 2
  - Danny Lamego, Record Label:Josie (Folder 1197, Box 15)
    - The Other Man, 1
    - No-No, 2
  - The Larks, Record Label:Dreamtone (Folder 1198, Box 15)
    - Danny Boy, 1
    - Without A Song, 2
  - The Larks, Record Label:Jett (Folder 1199, Box 15)
    - Love Me True, 1
    - Love You So, 2
  - The Larks, Record Label:Money (Folder 1200, Box 15)
    - The Jerk, 1